guarantybanking.com 2017-04-10

# 

                                                                                                             Rev. 12/2016
             WHAT DOES Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank in Michigan and Georgia) DO WITH YOUR
FACTS
             PERSONAL INFORMATION?
             Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
Why?         the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,
             and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
             The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with
             us. This information can include:
What?              • Social Security number and checking account information
                   • account balances and transaction history
                   • payment history and credit history
             All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In
             the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal
How?         information; the reasons Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank in Michigan and Georgia) chooses to share;
             and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                      Does Guaranty Bank (d/b/a
Reasons we can share your personal                                                       Can you limit this
                                                      BestBank in Michigan and
information                                                                              sharing?
                                                      Georgia) share?
 For our everyday business purposes –
 such as to process your transactions,
 maintain your account(s), respond to court                         YES                                 NO
 orders and legal investigations, or report to
 credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes –
                                                                    YES                                 NO
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial
                                                                    YES                                 NO
 companies
 For our affiliates’ everyday business
 purposes –
                                                                     NO                            We don’t share
 information about your transactions and
 experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business
 purposes –                                                          NO                            We don’t share
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                 NO                            We don’t share
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                 YES                                YES
                    •  Call 1-800-235-4636
                    •  For loan customers, press option 1,2,0
To limit            •  For deposit customers, press option 8,0
our           Please note:
sharing       If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
              notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in
              this notice.
              However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

Page 2
Questions?                                  Call 1-800-235-4636
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?               Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank in Michigan and Georgia).
What we do
                                            To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
How does Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank
                                            and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
in Michigan and Georgia) protect my
                                            These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
personal information?
                                            and buildings.
                                            We collect your personal information, for example, when you
                                                 • open an account or show your government-issued ID
How does Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank
in Michigan and Georgia) collect my
                                                 • apply for a loan or give us your contact information
personal information?                            • make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                            We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                            credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
                                            Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                 • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                     information about your creditworthiness
 Why can’t I limit all sharing?                  • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                 • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                            State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                            rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an
                                            Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
account I hold jointly with someone else?
Definitions
                                            Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                            financial and nonfinancial companies.
Affiliates
                                                 • Guaranty Bank (d/b/a BestBank in Michigan and Georgia)
                                                     does not share with our affiliates.
                                            Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                            be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Nonaffiliates
                                                 • Nonaffiliates we share with can include auto loan referral
                                                     companies.
                                            A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                            together market financial products or services to you.
Joint marketing                                  • Our joint marketing partners include companies such as
                                                     credit card companies, insurance companies, merchant
                                                     service companies and auto loan referral companies.
Other important information
Guaranty Bank does business as BestBank in Georgia and Michigan.
